Ida: And for me, personally, I, I grew up, sort of, all over the world,
we moved to a different country every three years of my life.
Ben: Yeah, yeah, no, I agree. I mean, for me, I’ve got, I’ve got a young son
who’s about to start school, er, later this year and so we’ve had to try and choose a school for him.
Ben: And then there was one school in particular that really stood out
and one of the reasons was because,
not only do they have lots of different languages, cultures, backgrounds…
Ida: That reminds me of an experience I had in school in first grade when I was living in Uruguay,…
Ida: …and it’s just really important, and I think it just – I then become very aware,
when I am in a place that is…not that, and it makes me slightly uncomfortable,
sort of, I don’t know…